export default [
    {
        question: "What tag does all of your HTML code go inside of?",
        answers: ["&lt;body&gt;", "&lt;html&gt;", "&lt;head&gt;", "&lt;h1&gt;"],
        correct: 1,
        value: 1000
    },
    {
        question: "What CSS property changes the text color?",
        answers: ["text-color", "font-color", "color", "background-color"],
        correct: 2,
        value: 1500
    },
    {
        question: "What Javascript function lets you type in a string?",
        answers: ["prompt()", "input()", "alert()", "string()"],
        correct: 0,
        value: 2500
    },
    {
        question: "Which tag makes a link to another web page?",
        answers: ["&lt;href&gt;", "&lt;link&gt;", "&lt;p&gt;", "&lt;a&gt;"],
        correct: 3,
        value: 5000
    },
    {
        question: "How do you define an array in Javascript?",
        answers: ["{1, 2, 3}", "(1, 2, 3)", "&lt;1, 2, 3&gt;", "[1, 2, 3]"],
        correct: 3,
        value: 15000
    },
    {
        question: "Which CSS property is used for curved edges?",
        answers: ["border-curve", "border-radius", "rounded-edge", "rounded-border"],
        correct: 1,
        value: 25000
    },
    {
        question: "What tag goes in the head for a mobile site?",
        answers: ["&lt;meta&gt;", "&lt;mobile&gt;", "&lt;device-width&gt;", "&lt;viewport&gt;"],
        correct: 0,
        value: 50000
    },
    {
        question: "What CSS will make an element double in size?",
        answers: ["size: 200%", "scale: 2", "transform: scale(2)", "transform: grow(2)"],
        correct: 2,
        value: 150000
    },
    {
        question: "What Javascript function is used to create a delay?",
        answers: ["pause()", "setDelay()", "wait()", "setTimeout()"],
        correct: 3,
        value: 250000
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a block-level element by default?",
        answers: ["&lt;div&gt;", "&lt;ul&gt;", "&lt;img&gt;", "&lt;p&gt;"],
        correct: 2,
        value: 500000
    },
];
